Guide to the Time Inc. Time Editorial Records 1938-2009 MS 3009-RG 7
New-York Historical Society
- Series I.A. Managing Editor Otto Fuerbringer Files, 1939-1985 (bulk 1950-1974); 15 Linear feet in 16 record cartons
  - Subseries I.A.3. Newstours, 1963-1965; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    - 1965: Time News Tour of Asia, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 1260, Folder 15-19)
  - Subseries I.A.4. Speeches, 1952-1974; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Speeches contains transcripts and notes along with invitations, correspondence, event ephemera, and news clippings. The majority of speeches are in the General files in reverse chronological order and include interviews. Fuerbringer gave speeches at conferences, universities, and professional associations outside of Time Inc. such as The Annenberg School of Communications, Concordia Theological Seminary, The Dallas Knife and Fork Club, and Suburban Newspaper Publishers Seminar. He also gave speeches at the Time Ad Convention and to Time staff. Interviews include "Firing Line with William F. Buckley Jr." on WOR-TV. Also included are some speeches by other Time Inc. staff such as Henry Luce III and Bernard Auer.
    Organized alphabetically with general files at the front.
    - General, 1952-1974 (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 1-7)
      1 audiotape reel (13.5 min.): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Olmsted Sound Studios, Inc. 1 East 54th St. N. Y. 22 PL 1-0890." On container: "With Me Today. 14-min. Interview, Alberse/Fuerbringer. Time-Life International. Released 6/7/63." Includes insert indicating the subject is "Time on its 40th Anniversary."
    - Drug Chemical and Allied Trades Association, 1967 (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 8)
    - Harvard Club of St. Louis, 1967 (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 9)
    - Time Staff, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 10)
    - Wagner College, undated (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 11)
  - Subseries I.A.5. Trips, 1957-1967; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Trips includes correspondence, itineraries, and written reports for Fuerbringer's business travel during his roles as assistant managing editor and managing editor for Time. While unrelated to Newstours, these trips seemed to be in order to observe the social and political climates and included meetings with heads of state, foreign ministers, and prominent business leaders.
    - 1957: Middle East (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 12-13)
    - 1959: England (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 14)
    - 1962: Europe (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 15)
    - 1962-1963: Reports (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 16)
    - 1963: Europe (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 17)
    - 1965: Europe (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 18)
    - 1966: Russia (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 19-20)
    - 1966: Russia (Offsite-box 2775, Folder 11)
    - 1967: Middle East (Offsite-box 1261, Folder 21)
- Series I.B. Managing Editor James R. Gaines Files, 1992-1996; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Biographical Note
  James R. Gaines joined Time as the Managing Editor in 1992 after holding editorial positions at People and Life. While in this role, Gaines served on the Online Steering Committee Educational Task Force. By January 1996, Gaines was promoted to Corporate Editor of Time Inc., a position he held until January 1997.
  The James R. Gaines Files include office files from his tenure as Managing Editor of Time and audiovisual material donated to the Time Inc. Archive by Gaines.
  The materials in this series are arranged into two subseries:
  Subseries I.B.1. Office Files
  Subseries I.B.2. Audiovisual
  - Subseries I.B.1. Office Files, 1992-1996; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Scope and Contents
    The Office Files primarily focus on James R. Gaines's tenure as Managing Editor of Time with a limited amount of materials related to his work as a member of the Time Inc. Online Steering Committee. Materials include article and magazine proposals, magazine dummies, quarterly reports on Time Digital, overviews and summaries of meetings, sales and usage reports, market evaluation and strategic assessment reports, budget reports, press releases, and correspondence and memoranda. Subjects discussed include the creation of new products, editorial decisions, magazine launches, project pitches, joint ventures with outside organizations, and staffing changes.
    Organized alphabetically with the file transfer memo at the front.
    - File Transfer Memorandum, 1996 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 1)
    - America Online, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 2-3)
    - America Online Newswatch Reports, 1995 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 4)
    - Capitol Hill Project, 1994 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 5)
    - Daily Doodle, 1994 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 6)
    - Digital Quarterly / Time Digital, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 7-8)
    - News on Demand Memoranda, 1994 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 9)
    - Time for Kids, 1992-1995 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 10-13)
    - Time for Kids: Covers, 1994 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 14)
    - Time for Kids: Prototype, 1994 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 15)
    - Time for Kids: Survey Results, 1995 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 16)
    - Time Japan, 1993 (Offsite-box 775, Folder 17)
    - Time Japan [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
  - Subseries I.B.2. Audiovisual, 1993, undated; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    The Audiovisual subseries contains videocassettes, audiocassettes, and one audiotape reel donated to the Time Inc. Archive by Gaines. The subject of many of the tapes is INTV, an unknown abbreviation. Other subjects related to the work that Gaines did as Managing Editor of Time as well as music from "10-10 Wins," a radio show produced by CBS radio.
    Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
    - Archives Transfer Forms, 2005 (Offsite-box 2591, Folder 1)
    - 1993 February 19: 1 audiocassette: analog, 1/8 in. tape. On container: "From Jim Gaines; Time Inc. 2/19/93; 1010 Wins; Radio Music." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 1)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "#1 3-16-93; Jim Gaines-Editors; CH 1 Wireless-Interference-Bad; Ch 2 Boom." On label: "#1 3-16-93 Jim Gaines -Editors CH1 Wireless - Interference CH2 Boom." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 2)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "101 IN. A2 (cu) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." On label: "A2 (cu) 3-16-93 Jim Gaines INTV CH 1&3 parallel." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 3)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "201 IN. A3 (cu) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." On label: "A3 (cu) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 4)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "301 IN. A4 (cu) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." On label: "A4 (cu) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 5)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "#5 3-16-93; Jim Gaines – Wild Sound." On label: "#5 3-16-93. Wild Sound. Jim Gaines." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 6)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "IB 101B. B2 (ws) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3." On label: "3-16-93 B2 Jim Gaines INTV CH 1&3." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 7)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "IB 201B. B3 (ws) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; Ch 1 & 3." On label: "B3 (ws) 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; Ch 1 & 3." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 8)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (Betacam SP). On container: "IB 301B. B4 3-16-93; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." On label: "3-16-93; B4; Jim Gaines INTV; CH 1 & 3 Parallel." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 9)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "Jim Gaines INTV; 3-16-93; Tape #1; Includes Tapes A2 (cu) & A3 (cu); Audio CH1 & Ch2." On label: "Jim Gaines INTV; 3-16-93; Tape #1; Includes Tapes A2 (cu) & A3 (cu); Audio CH1 & Ch2." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 10)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "Jim Gaines INTV, 3-16-93; Tape #2; Includes Tapes A4 & B2 (ws); Audio CH 1 & 2." On label: "Jim Gaines INTV, 3-16-93; Tape #2; Includes Tapes A4 & B2 (ws); Audio CH 1 & 2." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 11)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "Jim Gaines INTV; 3-16-93; Tape #3; Includes B3 (ws) & B4; Audio CH 1 & 2." On label: "Jim Gaines INTV; 3-16-93; Tape #3; Includes B3 (ws) & B4; Audio CH 1 & 2." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 12)
    - 1993 March 16: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "Jim Gaines; Editor; Wild Sound; 3-16-93; Tape #4; Includes tapes 1 & 5; CH1 Wireless Interference-Bad, CH 2 Bloom." On label: "Jim Gaines; Editor; Wild Sound; 3-16-93; Tape #4; Includes tapes 1 & 5; CH1 Wireless Interference-Bad, CH 2 Bloom." (Offsite-box 2591, Item 13)
    - 1993 March 25: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. Partial container label: "Fallon McElligott. 3/25/93. Time Magazine." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 1)
      Contains eight news spots: Roe vs. Wade, Colorado River, Somebody's Watching, L.A. Riots, Angry Voter/Rev, Losing the Battle, Balkans, and Africa.
    - 1993 March 29: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "3/29/93 Time Magazine; Fallon McElligott; Fischer Edit; Magazine Covers; 35mm Slide X-Fer; Just Time Covers." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 2)
    - 1993 March 29: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "3/29/93 Time Magazine; Fallon McElligott; Fischer Edit; --> Magazine Covers; 35mm Slide X-Fer." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 3)
    - 1993 March 30: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container: "3/30/93 Time Magazine; Fallon McElligott; Fischer Edit; Slide X-fer Fix Test; Time Covers Only." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 4)
    - 1993 June 25: 1 audiotape reel: analog, 15 ips, stereo; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "6-25-93; Fischer Edit; Fallon, Time Magazine; "Time Marches On", Master Mix." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 5)
    - 1993 July 13: 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On container spine: "Jim Gaines. Time News Footage. 7.13.93." On label: "Time News Footage; Dub 7/13/93." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 6)
    - 1993 August 13: 1 audiocassette: digital, stereo, 1/8 in. tape. Partial container label: "From Jim Gaines; Fallon McElligott; Time Magazine Video; August 13, 1993; 1. 'Time Marches On.'" On label: "Time Magazine; 'Time Marches On.' 8/13/93." (Offsite-box 2592, Item 7)
    - Undated: 1 audiocassette: analog, 1/8 in. tape. On container" "Gaines' Original. On label: "Tom's Gaines Tape.", 1993? (Offsite-box 2592, Item 8)
- Series II.A. Executive Editor J. Dana Tasker Files on Covers, 1942-1961; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Biographical / Historical
  J. Dana Tasker handled the retention or disposition of Time's cover art. While Time only acquired the first publication rights for its cover art, it might purchase the original work to gift. Otherwise the artist could sell the original as they wanted. Time frequently sent as a gift, or presented, cover art to the subject or a related interested party or organization as a gesture of good will, for promotion value, or to continue a relationship with a good source. Time executives were less likely to gift if they did not think there was any value to the gesture, did not considered the portrait to be a good likeness, if the art was in multiple pieces and therefore not one original to give, or if the artist wouldn't part with it or had another buyer already. Presenters included cofounder Henry R. Luce, Editorial Vice President Eric Hodgins, Publisher P. I. Prentice, or any other Time employee who had a specific relationship with the recipient. Early cover artists for Time were Boris Artzybasheff, Ernest Hamlin Baker, Boris Chaliapin, and Guy Rowe.
  J. Dana Tasker's files includes the memoranda, correspondence and invoices related to the retention or disposition of Time's cover art. Memoranda from him to Publisher James Linen discuss whether or not original art should go to the subject and the reasons for the decisions. Inventories include reports from the Business Manager James Thomason on covers still in the "bank" for future use with responses from Tasker on which ones to "kill," removing them from storage by returning to the artist or other method. Records also include other interoffice memoranda arranging presentations, correspondence to and from the gift recipients, and framing and shipping invoices.
  - Cover Inventories, 1943-1951 (Offsite-box 2562, Folder 12-13)
  - Cover Inventories, 1952-1961 (Offsite-box 2563, Folder 1)
  - Cover Presentations Correspondence, 1942-1957 (Offsite-box 2563, Folder 2-14)
  - Cover Shipments, 1946-1957 (Offsite-box 2563, Folder 15)
- Series II.B. Executive Editor Edward Jamieson Files, 1957-1986; 37 Linear feet in 37 record cartons
  According to the press release announcing his promotion in 1976 to Executive Editor, Edward Jamieson started as a writer at Time in 1954. Time promoted him to a senior editor position in 1963, then Assistant Managing Editor in 1969. His administrative assistant was Elizabeth Waite.
  Edward Jamieson's files span from his roles as Time Senior Editor, Assistant Managing Editor, and Executive Editor with some collected materials having earlier dates. Records include his correspondence, subject files covering decisions made by him and his office, company reference materials mainly collected by his assistant, and files on his management of Time Editorial personnel.
  Organized into four series:
  Subseries II.B.1. Correspondence and Memoranda
  Subseries II.B.2. Subject Files
  Subseries II.B.3. Printed Matter
  Subseries II.B.4. Personnel
  - Subseries II.B.1. Correspondence and Memoranda, 1968-1984; 10.5 Linear feet in 11 record cartons
    Correspondence and Memoranda include lists of correspondents' locations; internal and external correspondence to Jamieson's assistant Elizabeth Waite; reports on story and page counts; memoranda from Corporate Editorial; memoranda to staff from Jamieson or Time Inc. executives; errors reports; Time staff changes; masthead changes; corporate and editorial policies; meeting agendas; some Time Letters reports; some polls and reports from Louis Harris. The 1960s contain some material from James Keough who was also an Executive Editor but left Time Inc. in 1968 to be an aide to Nixon. Corporate Memos includes information on employee benefits; shareholder reports; staff events; and staff changes. Memoranda to specific people at Time include Managing Editor Henry Grunwald, Assistant Managing Editor and Time Life News Service Chief Murray Gart, Production Directors Don Barr and Hub Smith, and Assistant Business Manager Harriet Watt. Some months or years of correspondence are not present.
    Organized chronologically based on the original arrangement.
    - Correspondence: Personal, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3250, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence, 1968 September-1969 April (Offsite-box 2434)
    - Correspondence, 1969 May-October (Offsite-box 2435)
    - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1969 June (Offsite-box R39)
    - Correspondence, 1969 November-December (Offsite-box 2436, Folder 1-4)
      November includes audiovisual material from an enveloped labeled "Kalem speech."
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "One."
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Two."
    - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1969 November (Offsite-box R39)
      April-June includes transcipts from an editors dinner.
    - Memoranda: Staff, 1969 (Offsite-box 3250, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1970 January-December (Offsite-box 3250, Folder 3-12)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1970 (Offsite-box 3250, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1970 (Offsite-box 3250, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1971 January-June (Offsite-box 3250, Folder 16-22)
    - Correspondence, 1971 July-December (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 1-2)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1971 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 3-4)
    - Memoranda: Staff, 1971 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972 January-November (Offsite-box 2436, Folder 5-17)
    - Correspondence, 1972 December (Offsite-box 2437, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1972 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 6-7)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1972 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: Don Barr and Hub Smith, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 2437, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1973 January-December (Offsite-box 2437, Folder 3-15)
    - Correspondence: Business Office, 1973 (Offsite-box 2437, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1973 (Offsite-box 2437, Folder 17-18)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1973 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1973 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda: Harriet Watt, 1973 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1974 January-December (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 4-16)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1974 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 17-18)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1974 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Murray Gart, 1974 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Hub Smith, 1974 (Offsite-box 2438, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1975 January-December (Offsite-box 2439, Folder 1-6)
    - Correspondence: Marshall Loeb, 1975 (Offsite-box 2439, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1975 (Offsite-box 2439, Folder 8-9)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1975 (Offsite-box 2439, Folder 10-11)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January-May (Offsite-box 2439, Folder 12-16)
    - Correspondence, 1976 June (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1976 August-December (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 2-6)
    - Correspondence: Elizabeth Waite, 1976 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1976 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 8-9)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1976 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 10-12)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Alwyn Lee, 1977 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1977 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 14-15)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1977 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 16-17)
    - Memoranda: Henry Grunwald, 1977 (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1978 January-February (Offsite-box 2440, Folder 19-20)
    - Correspondence, 1978 March-September (Offsite-box 2441, Folder 1-5)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1978 (Offsite-box 2441, Folder 6-8)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1978 (Offsite-box 2441, Folder 9-10)
    - Memoranda: Henry Grunwald, 1978 (Offsite-box 2441, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1979 January-September (Offsite-box 2441, Folder 12-16)
    - Memoranda: General, 1979 (Offsite-box 2441, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1979 (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 1-3)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit [empty], 1979 (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1980 (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1981 January-December (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 7-11)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1981 (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 12-13)
    - Memoranda: Time Edit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2442, Folder 14-15)
    - Correspondence, 1984 June-August (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 1-3)
    - Memoranda: Corporate, 1984 (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 4-5)
  - Subseries II.B.2. Subject Files, 1957-1985; 17.75 Linear feet in 19 record cartons
    Subject Files covering decisions made by Jamieson and his office on editorial areas such as overseeing content close dates within production scheduling, masthead changes, choosing the Man of the Year, cover choices and scheduling, tracking newsstand sales and comparisons with Newsweek, specific stories in various sections, political convention coverage, and daily office concerns.
    Organized chronologically based on the original arrangement with alphabetical arrangement within each year imposed.
    - 1957-1961: O'Neill, Martin (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 9)
    - 1962: Volume I, Number I Time Magazine (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 6)
    - 1963-1968: Staff Memoranda Distribution (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 7)
    - 1964: Staff List Distribution (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 8)
    - 1966: Floor Plans (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 10)
    - 1967: Cover Artists, approximately 1967 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 11)
    - 1967: Expense Accounts and Reports (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 12-13)
    - 1967: Time Essays List (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 14)
    - 1968: Ad Rates (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 9)
    - 1968: Bermuda Conference (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 15-16)
    - 1968: Binding (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 10)
    - 1968: Budget (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 11)
    - 1968: Circulation Department: Fox Hill (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 12)
    - 1968: Cover Artists: Rejected (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 17)
    - 1968: Cover Schedules (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 13)
    - 1968: Elections, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 18-19)
    - 1968: Election Schedule (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 14)
    - 1968: Employment (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 20)
    - 1968: Expense Account (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 21-22)
    - 1968: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 15-17)
    - 1968: Newstours: Asia: Itinerary (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 23)
    - 1968: Political Conventions: Republican (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 18)
    - 1968: Smith, DeWitt (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 19)
    - 1968: Study of Pix and Production Department (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 24)
    - 1969: Art Cover, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 25)
    - 1969: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 26)
    - 1969: Chaliapin, Boris: Travel (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 27)
    - 1969: Cover Schedules (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 20)
    - 1969: Cover Suggestions (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 28)
    - 1969: Editorial Close Report (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 29-30)
    - 1969: Futures List (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 31)
    - 1969: Keogh, James: January Dinner (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 21)
    - 1969: Keogh, James: Pictures (Offsite-box 3251, Folder 32)
    - 1969: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 1-3)
    - 1969: Newsstand Sales (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 4)
    - 1969: News Wire (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 5)
    - 1969: Noise Pollution (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 22)
    - 1969: Pending Matters (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 23)
    - 1969: Proposed Ecology Cover (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 6)
    - 1969: Reprints and Permissions (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 7)
    - 1969: Senior Editors Conference: Nassau (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 24)
    - 1969: Time Annual (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 8)
    - 1969: Time-Life Books (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 9)
    - 1969: Time Montreal Editorial (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 10)
    - 1969: Time / Newsweek Comparisons (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 11)
    - 1969: Time / Newsweek Comparisons (Offsite-box 2443, Folder 25)
    - 1969: Overseas News Service Bureaus and Stringers (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 1)
    - 1969: Trip: South America (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 2)
    - 1969: White House Correspondents' Dinner (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 3)
    - 1970: Atlo: Atlantic Edition (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 12)
    - 1970: Black-and-white Page Figures (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 13)
    - 1970: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 14)
    - 1970: Byline (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 15)
    - 1970: Chaliapin, Boris (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 16)
    - 1970: Cost of Sunday Edit Corrections (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 17)
    - 1970: Cover Engravings (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 4)
    - 1970: Covers and Cover Closings (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 18-21)
    - 1970: Demarest, Michael: Farewell Dinner (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 22)
    - 1970: Demarest, Michael: Memo on Word Usage (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 23)
    - 1970: Drapkin, Arnold: Reduction of Time Border (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 24)
    - 1970: Editorial Close Report (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 25-26)
    - 1970: Essays with Bylines (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 27)
    - 1970: Expense Accounts, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 28-29)
    - 1970: Grunwald, Henry: Itinerary (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 30)
    - 1970: Hemisphere Club (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 31)